<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MovieCatalogue</string>

    <!-- main activity -->
    <string name="main_activity_title">Catalogue</string>
    <string name="tab_layout_movie">Movies</string>
    <string name="tab_layout_tv_show">TV Shows</string>
    <string name="movie_listing">Movie Listing</string>
    <string name="tv_show_listing">TV Show Listing</string>
    <string name="movie_title_placeholder">Movie Name</string>
    <string name="movie_year_placeholder">2019</string>
    <string name="movie_figure_placeholder">Calvin Tandra</string>

    <!-- detail activity -->
    <string name="detail_activity_title">Details</string>
    <string name="detail_category">Category</string>
    <string name="detail_category_movie">Movie</string>
    <string name="detail_category_tv_show">TV Show</string>
    <string name="detail_year">Release Year</string>
    <string name="detail_figure">Figure</string>
    <string name="detail_figure_director">Director</string>
    <string name="detail_figure_creator">Creator</string>
    <string name="sample_category">Sample Category</string>
    <string name="sample_title">Sample Title</string>
    <string name="sample_figure">Sample Figure</string>
    <string name="sample_year">Sample Year</string>
    <string name="sample_description">Sample Description</string>
    <string name="movie_poster_content_description">Movie Poster</string>

    <!-- language fragment -->
    <string name="language_fragment_title">Languages</string>
    <string name="language_options_en">English</string>
    <string name="language_options_in">Indonesian</string>
    <string name="btn_language_choose">Choose Language</string>
    <string name="language_toast_chosen">Successfully changed the application\'s language!</string>

    <!-- menu -->
    <string name="menu_language">Change Language</string>

    <!-- titles -->
    <string-array name="movie_title">
        <item name="A Star is Born">A Star is Born</item>
        <item name="Alita: Battle Angel">Alita: Battle Angel</item>
        <item name="Aquaman">Aquaman</item>
        <item name="Avengers: Infinity War">Avengers: Infinity War</item>
        <item name="Bohemian Rhapsody">Bohemian Rhapsody</item>
        <item name="Cold Pursuit">Cold Pursuit</item>
        <item name="Creed II">Creed II</item>
        <item name="Fantastic Beasts: The Crimes of Grindelwald">Fantastic Beasts: The Crimes of Grindelwald</item>
        <item name="Glass">Glass</item>
        <item name="How to Train Your Dragon: The Hidden World">How to Train Your Dragon: The Hidden World</item>
        <item name="Mary Queen of Scots">Mary Queen of Scots</item>
        <item name="Master Z: Ip Man Legacy">Master Z: Ip Man Legacy</item>
        <item name="Mortal Engines">Mortal Engines</item>
        <item name="Overlord">Overlord</item>
        <item name="Ralph Breaks the Internet">Ralph Breaks the Internet</item>
        <item name="Robin Hood">Robin Hood</item>
        <item name="Serenity">Serenity</item>
        <item name="Spider-Man: Into the Spider-Verse">Spider-Man: Into the Spider-Verse</item>
        <item name="T-34">T-34</item>
        <item name="Arrow">Arrow</item>
        <item name="Doom Patrol">Doom Patrol</item>
        <item name="Dragon Ball">Dragon Ball</item>
        <item name="Fairy Tail">Fairy Tail</item>
        <item name="Family Guy">Family Guy</item>
        <item name="Game of Thrones">Game of Thrones</item>
        <item name="Gotham">Gotham</item>
        <item name="Grey's Anatomy">Grey\'s Anatomy</item>
        <item name="Hanna">Hanna</item>
        <item name="Marvel's Iron Fist">Marvel\'s Iron Fist</item>
        <item name="Naruto Shippuuden">Naruto Shippuuden</item>
        <item name="NCIS">NCIS</item>
        <item name="Riverdale">Riverdale</item>
        <item name="Shameless">Shameless</item>
        <item name="Supergirl">Supergirl</item>
        <item name="Supernatural">Supernatural</item>>
        <item name="The Flash">The Flash</item>
        <item name="The Simpsons">The Simpsons</item>
        <item name="The Umbrella Academy">The Umbrella Academy</item>
        <item name="The Walking Dead">The Walking Dead</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- descriptions -->
    <string-array name="movie_description">
        <item name="A Star is Born">
            Seasoned musician Jackson Maine discovers — and falls in love with — struggling artist Ally. She has just about
            given up on her dream to make it big as a singer — until Jack coaxes her into the spotlight. But even as Ally\'s
            career takes off, the personal side of their relationship is breaking down, as Jack fights an ongoing battle with
            his own internal demons.
        </item>
        <item name="Alita: Battle Angel">
            When Alita awakens with no memory of who she is in a future world she does not recognize, she is taken in by Ido,
            a compassionate doctor who realizes that somewhere in this abandoned cyborg shell is the heart and soul of a young
            woman with an extraordinary past.</item>
        <item name="Aquaman">
            Once home to the most advanced civilization on Earth, Atlantis is now an underwater kingdom ruled by the
            power-hungry King Orm. With a vast army at his disposal, Orm plans to conquer the remaining oceanic people and then
            the surface world. Standing in his way is Arthur Curry, Orm\'s half-human, half-Atlantean brother and true heir to
            the throne.
        </item>
        <item name="Avengers: Infinity War">
            As the Avengers and their allies have continued to protect the world from threats too large for any one hero to
            handle, a new danger has emerged from the cosmic shadows: Thanos. A despot of intergalactic infamy, his goal is to
            collect all six Infinity Stones, artifacts of unimaginable power, and use them to inflict his twisted will on all
            of reality. Everything the Avengers have fought for has led up to this moment - the fate of Earth and existence
            itself has never been more uncertain.
        </item>
        <item name="Bohemian Rhapsody">
            Singer Freddie Mercury, guitarist Brian May, drummer Roger Taylor and bass guitarist John Deacon take the music
            world by storm when they form the rock \'n\' roll band Queen in 1970. Hit songs become instant classics. When
            Mercury\'s increasingly wild lifestyle starts to spiral out of control, Queen soon faces its greatest challenge yet
            – finding a way to keep the band together amid the success and excess.
        </item>
        <item name="Cold Pursuit">
            Nels Coxman, a snowplow driver recently awarded the title of citizen of the year, triggers a series of violence and
            misunderstandings between two rival gangs after he starts avenging his son\'s death.
        </item>
        <item name="Creed II">
            Between personal obligations and training for his next big fight against an opponent with ties to his family\'s past,
            Adonis Creed is up against the challenge of his life.
        </item>
        <item name="Fantastic Beasts: The Crimes of Grindelwald">
            Gellert Grindelwald has escaped imprisonment and has begun gathering followers to his cause—elevating wizards above
            all non-magical beings. The only one capable of putting a stop to him is the wizard he once called his closest
            friend, Albus Dumbledore. However, Dumbledore will need to seek help from the wizard who had thwarted Grindelwald
            once before, his former student Newt Scamander, who agrees to help, unaware of the dangers that lie ahead. Lines are
            drawn as love and loyalty are tested, even among the truest friends and family, in an increasingly divided
            wizarding world.</item>
        <item name="Glass">
            In a series of escalating encounters, security guard David Dunn uses his supernatural abilities to track Kevin
            Wendell Crumb, a disturbed man who has twenty-four personalities. Meanwhile, the shadowy presence of Elijah Price
            emerges as an orchestrator who holds secrets critical to both men.
        </item>
        <item name="How to Train Your Dragon: The Hidden World">
            As Hiccup fulfills his dream of creating a peaceful dragon utopia, Toothless\’ discovery of an untamed, elusive
            mate draws the Night Fury away. When danger mounts at home and Hiccup\’s reign as village chief is tested, both
            dragon and rider must make impossible decisions to save their kind.
        </item>
        <item name="Mary Queen of Scots">
            In 1561, Mary Stuart, widow of the King of France, returns to Scotland, reclaims her rightful throne and menaces the
            future of Queen Elizabeth I as ruler of England, because she has a legitimate claim to the English throne. Betrayals,
            rebellions, conspiracies and their own life choices imperil both Queens. They experience the bitter cost of power,
            until their tragic fate is finally fulfilled.
        </item>
        <item name="Master Z: Ip Man Legacy">
            After being defeated by Ip Man, Cheung Tin Chi is attempting to keep a low profile. While going about his business,
            he gets into a fight with a foreigner by the name of Davidson, who is a big boss behind the bar district. Tin Chi
            fights hard with Wing Chun and earns respect.
        </item>
        <item name="Mortal Engines">
            Many thousands of years in the future, Earth\’s cities roam the globe on huge wheels, devouring each other in a
            struggle for ever diminishing resources. On one of these massive traction cities, the old London, Tom Natsworthy
            has an unexpected encounter with a mysterious young woman from the wastelands who will change the course of his life
            forever.
        </item>
        <item name="Overlord">
            France, June 1944. On the eve of D-Day, some American paratroopers fall behind enemy lines after their aircraft
            crashes while on a mission to destroy a radio tower in a small village near the beaches of Normandy. After reaching
            their target, the surviving paratroopers realise that, in addition to fighting the Nazi troops that patrol the
            village, they also must fight against something else.
        </item>
        <item name="Ralph Breaks the Internet">
            Video game bad guy Ralph and fellow misfit Vanellope von Schweetz must risk it all by traveling to the World Wide Web
            in search of a replacement part to save Vanellope\'s video game, "Sugar Rush." In way over their heads, Ralph and
            Vanellope rely on the citizens of the internet — the netizens — to help navigate their way, including an
            entrepreneur named Yesss, who is the head algorithm and the heart and soul of trend-making site BuzzzTube.
        </item>
        <item name="Robin Hood">
            A war-hardened Crusader and his Moorish commander mount an audacious revolt against the corrupt English crown.
        </item>
        <item name="Serenity">
            Baker Dill is a fishing boat captain leading tours off a tranquil, tropical enclave called Plymouth Island. His
            quiet life is shattered, however, when his ex-wife Karen tracks him down with a desperate plea for help.
        </item>
        <item name="Spider-Man: Into the Spider-Verse">
            Miles Morales is juggling his life between being a high school student and being a spider-man. When Wilson "Kingpin"
            Fisk uses a super collider, others from across the Spider-Verse are transported to this dimension.
        </item>
        <item name="T-34">
            In 1944, a courageous group of Russian soldiers managed to escape from German captivity in a half-destroyed legendary
            T-34 tank. Those were the times of unforgettable bravery, fierce fighting, unbreakable love, and legendary miracles.
        </item>
        <item name="Arrow">
            Spoiled billionaire playboy Oliver Queen is missing and presumed dead when his yacht is lost at sea. He returns five
            years later a changed man, determined to clean up the city as a hooded vigilante armed with a bow.
        </item>
        <item name="Doom Patrol">
            The Doom Patrol’s members each suffered horrible accidents that gave them superhuman abilities — but also left them
            scarred and disfigured. Traumatized and downtrodden, the team found purpose through The Chief, who brought them
            together to investigate the weirdest phenomena in existence — and to protect Earth from what they find.
        </item>
        <item name="Dragon Ball">
            Long ago in the mountains, a fighting master known as Gohan discovered a strange boy whom he named Goku. Gohan raised
            him and trained Goku in martial arts until he died. The young and very strong boy was on his own, but easily managed.
            Then one day, Goku met a teenage girl named Bulma, whose search for the dragon balls brought her to Goku\'s home.
            Together, they set off to find all seven dragon balls in an adventure that would change Goku\'s life forever. See how
            Goku met his life long friends Bulma, Yamcha, Krillin, Master Roshi and more. And see his adventures as a boy,
            all leading up to Dragonball Z and later Dragonball GT.
        </item>
        <item name="Fairy Tail">
            Lucy is a 17-year-old girl, who wants to be a full-fledged mage. One day when visiting Harujion Town, she meets
            Natsu, a young man who gets sick easily by any type of transportation. But Natsu isn\'t just any ordinary kid, he\'s
            a member of one of the world\'s most infamous mage guilds: Fairy Tail.
        </item>
        <item name="Family Guy">
            Sick, twisted, politically incorrect and Freakin\' Sweet animated series featuring the adventures of the
            dysfunctional Griffin family. Bumbling Peter and long-suffering Lois have three kids. Stewie (a brilliant but
            sadistic baby bent on killing his mother and taking over the world), Meg (the oldest, and is the most unpopular girl
            in town) and Chris (the middle kid, he\'s not very bright but has a passion for movies). The final member of the
            family is Brian - a talking dog and much more than a pet, he keeps Stewie in check whilst sipping Martinis and
            sorting through his own life issues.
        </item>
        <item name="Game of Thrones">
            Seven noble families fight for control of the mythical land of Westeros. Friction between the houses leads to
            full-scale war. All while a very ancient evil awakens in the farthest north. Amidst the war, a neglected military
            order of misfits, the Night\'s Watch, is all that stands between the realms of men and icy horrors beyond.
        </item>
        <item name="Gotham">
            Everyone knows the name Commissioner Gordon. He is one of the crime world\'s greatest foes, a man whose reputation is synonymous with law and
            order. But what is known of Gordon\'s story and his rise from rookie detective to Police Commissioner? What did it take to navigate the
            multiple layers of corruption that secretly ruled Gotham City, the spawning ground of the world\'s most iconic villains? And what circumstances
            created them – the larger-than-life personas who would become Catwoman, The Penguin, The Riddler, Two-Face and The Joker?
        </item>
        <item name="Grey's Anatomy">
            Follows the personal and professional lives of a group of doctors at Seattle\’s Grey Sloan Memorial Hospital.
        </item>
        <item name="Hanna">
            This thriller and coming-of-age drama follows the journey of an extraordinary young girl as she evades the
            relentless pursuit of an off-book CIA agent and tries to unearth the truth behind who she is. Based on the 2011
            Joe Wright film.
        </item>
        <item name="Marvel's Iron Fist">
            Danny Rand resurfaces 15 years after being presumed dead. Now, with the power of the Iron Fist, he seeks to reclaim
            his past and fulfill his destiny.
        </item>
        <item name="Naruto Shippuuden">
            Naruto Shippuuden is the continuation of the original animated TV series Naruto. The story revolves around an older
            and slightly more matured Uzumaki Naruto and his quest to save his friend Uchiha Sasuke from the grips of the
            snake-like Shinobi, Orochimaru. After 2 and a half years Naruto finally returns to his village of Konoha, and sets
            about putting his ambitions to work, though it will not be easy, as He has amassed a few (more dangerous) enemies,
            in the likes of the shinobi organization: Akatsuki.
        </item>
        <item name="NCIS">
            From murder and espionage to terrorism and stolen submarines, a team of special agents investigates any crime that
            has a shred of evidence connected to Navy and Marine Corps personnel, regardless of rank or position.
        </item>
        <item name="Riverdale">
            Set in the present, the series offers a bold, subversive take on Archie, Betty, Veronica and their friends,
            exploring the surreality of small-town life, the darkness and weirdness bubbling beneath Riverdale\’s wholesome
            facade.
        </item>
        <item name="Shameless">
            Chicagoan Frank Gallagher is the proud single dad of six smart, industrious, independent kids, who without him would
            be… perhaps better off. When Frank\'s not at the bar spending what little money they have, he\'s passed out on the
            floor. But the kids have found ways to grow up in spite of him. They may not be like any family you know, but they
            make no apologies for being exactly who they are.
        </item>
        <item name="Supergirl">
            Twenty-four-year-old Kara Zor-El, who was taken in by the Danvers family when she was 13 after being sent away from
            Krypton, must learn to embrace her powers after previously hiding them. The Danvers teach her to be careful with her
            powers, until she has to reveal them during an unexpected disaster, setting her on her journey of heroism.
        </item>
        <item name="Supernatural">
            When they were boys, Sam and Dean Winchester lost their mother to a mysterious and demonic supernatural force.
            Subsequently, their father raised them to be soldiers. He taught them about the paranormal evil that lives in the
            dark corners and on the back roads of America… and he taught them how to kill it. Now, the Winchester brothers
            crisscross the country in their \'67 Chevy Impala, battling every kind of supernatural threat they encounter along
            the way.
        </item>
        <item name="The Flash">
            After a particle accelerator causes a freak storm, CSI Investigator Barry Allen is struck by lightning and falls
            into a coma. Months later he awakens with the power of super speed, granting him the ability to move through Central
            City like an unseen guardian angel. Though initially excited by his newfound powers, Barry is shocked to discover he
            is not the only "meta-human" who was created in the wake of the accelerator explosion — and not everyone is using
            their new powers for good. Barry partners with S.T.A.R. Labs and dedicates his life to protect the innocent. For now,
            only a few close friends and associates know that Barry is literally the fastest man alive, but it won\'t be long
            before the world learns what Barry Allen has become… The Flash.
        </item>
        <item name="The Simpsons">
            Set in Springfield, the average American town, the show focuses on the antics and everyday adventures of the Simpson
            family; Homer, Marge, Bart, Lisa and Maggie, as well as a virtual cast of thousands. Since the beginning, the series
            has been a pop culture icon, attracting hundreds of celebrities to guest star. The show has also made name for
            itself in its fearless satirical take on politics, media and American life in general.
        </item>
        <item name="The Umbrella Academy">
            A dysfunctional family of superheroes comes together to solve the mystery of their father\'s death, the threat of the
            apocalypse and more.
        </item>
        <item name="The Walking Dead">
            Sheriff\'s deputy Rick Grimes awakens from a coma to find a post-apocalyptic world dominated by flesh-eating zombies.
            He sets out to find his family and encounters many other survivors along the way.
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- posters -->
    <array name="movie_poster">
        <item name="A Star is Born">@drawable/poster_a_star_is_born</item>
        <item name="Alita: Battle Angel">@drawable/poster_alita</item>
        <item name="Aquaman">@drawable/poster_aquaman</item>
        <item name="Avengers: Infinity War">@drawable/poster_avengers_infinity_war</item>
        <item name="Bohemian Rhapsody">@drawable/poster_bohemian</item>
        <item name="Cold Pursuit">@drawable/poster_cold_pursuit</item>
        <item name="Creed II">@drawable/poster_creed_ii</item>
        <item name="Fantastic Beasts: The Crimes of Grindelwald">@drawable/poster_fantastic_beasts
        </item>
        <item name="Glass">@drawable/poster_glass</item>
        <item name="How to Train Your Dragon: The Hidden World">@drawable/poster_how_to_train</item>
        <item name="Mary Queen of Scots">@drawable/poster_mary_queen</item>
        <item name="Master Z: Ip Man Legacy">@drawable/poster_master_z</item>
        <item name="Mortal Engines">@drawable/poster_mortal_engines</item>
        <item name="Overlord">@drawable/poster_overlord</item>
        <item name="Ralph Breaks the Internet">@drawable/poster_ralph</item>
        <item name="Robin Hood">@drawable/poster_robin_hood</item>
        <item name="Serenity">@drawable/poster_serenity</item>
        <item name="Spider-Man: Into the Spider-Verse">@drawable/poster_spiderman</item>
        <item name="T-34">@drawable/poster_t34</item>
        <item name="Arrow">@drawable/poster_arrow</item>
        <item name="Doom Patrol">@drawable/poster_doom_patrol</item>
        <item name="Dragon Ball">@drawable/poster_dragon_ball</item>
        <item name="Fairy Tail">@drawable/poster_fairy_tail</item>
        <item name="Family Guy">@drawable/poster_family_guy</item>
        <item name="Game of Thrones">@drawable/poster_game_of_thrones</item>
        <item name="Gotham">@drawable/poster_gotham</item>
        <item name="Grey's Anatomy">@drawable/poster_grey_anatomy</item>
        <item name="Hanna">@drawable/poster_hanna</item>
        <item name="Marvel's Iron Fist">@drawable/poster_marvel_iron_fist</item>
        <item name="Naruto Shippuuden">@drawable/poster_naruto_shippudden</item>
        <item name="NCIS">@drawable/poster_ncis</item>
        <item name="Riverdale">@drawable/poster_riverdale</item>
        <item name="Shameless">@drawable/poster_shameless</item>
        <item name="Supergirl">@drawable/poster_supergirl</item>
        <item name="Supernatural">@drawable/poster_supernatural</item>>
        <item name="The Flash">@drawable/poster_the_flash</item>
        <item name="The Simpsons">@drawable/poster_the_simpsons</item>
        <item name="The Umbrella Academy">@drawable/poster_the_umbrella</item>
        <item name="The Walking Dead">@drawable/poster_the_walking_dead</item>
    </array>

    <!-- years -->
    <string-array name="movie_year">
        <item name="A Star is Born">2018</item>
        <item name="Alita: Battle Angel">2019</item>
        <item name="Aquaman">2018</item>
        <item name="Avengers: Infinity War">2018</item>
        <item name="Bohemian Rhapsody">2018</item>
        <item name="Cold Pursuit">2019</item>
        <item name="Creed II">2018</item>
        <item name="Fantastic Beasts: The Crimes of Grindelwald">2018</item>
        <item name="Glass">2019</item>
        <item name="How to Train Your Dragon: The Hidden World">2019</item>
        <item name="Mary Queen of Scots">2018</item>
        <item name="Master Z: Ip Man Legacy">2018</item>
        <item name="Mortal Engines">2018</item>
        <item name="Overlord">2018</item>
        <item name="Ralph Breaks the Internet">2018</item>
        <item name="Robin Hood">2018</item>
        <item name="Serenity">2019</item>
        <item name="Spider-Man: Into the Spider-Verse">2018</item>
        <item name="T-34">2018</item>
        <item name="Arrow">2012</item>
        <item name="Doom Patrol">2019</item>
        <item name="Dragon Ball">1986</item>
        <item name="Fairy Tail">2009</item>
        <item name="Family Guy">1999</item>
        <item name="Game of Thrones">2011</item>
        <item name="Gotham">2014</item>
        <item name="Grey's Anatomy">2005</item>
        <item name="Hanna">2019</item>
        <item name="Marvel's Iron Fist">2017</item>
        <item name="Naruto Shippuuden">2007</item>
        <item name="NCIS">2003</item>
        <item name="Riverdale">2017</item>
        <item name="Shameless">2011</item>
        <item name="Supergirl">2015</item>
        <item name="Supernatural">2005</item>>
        <item name="The Flash">2014</item>
        <item name="The Simpsons">1989</item>
        <item name="The Umbrella Academy">2019</item>
        <item name="The Walking Dead">2010</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- figures -->
    <string-array name="movie_figure">
        <item name="A Star is Born">Bradley Cooper</item>
        <item name="Alita: Battle Angel">Robert Rodriguez</item>
        <item name="Aquaman">James Wan</item>
        <item name="Avengers: Infinity War">Joe Russo</item>
        <item name="Bohemian Rhapsody">Bryan Singer</item>
        <item name="Cold Pursuit">Hans Petter Moland</item>
        <item name="Creed II">Steven Caple Jr.</item>
        <item name="Fantastic Beasts: The Crimes of Grindelwald">David Yates</item>
        <item name="Glass">M. Night Shyamalan</item>
        <item name="How to Train Your Dragon: The Hidden World">Dean DeBlois</item>
        <item name="Mary Queen of Scots">Josie Rourke</item>
        <item name="Master Z: Ip Man Legacy">Yuen Woo-ping</item>
        <item name="Mortal Engines">Christian Rivers</item>
        <item name="Overlord">Julius Avery</item>
        <item name="Ralph Breaks the Internet">Phil Johnston &amp; Rich Moore</item>
        <item name="Robin Hood">Otto Bathurst</item>
        <item name="Serenity">Steven Knight</item>
        <item name="Spider-Man: Into the Spider-Verse">Rodney Rothman</item>
        <item name="T-34">Aleksey Sidorov</item>
        <item name="Arrow">Greg Berlanti, Marc Guggenheim, &amp; Andrew Kreisberg</item>
        <item name="Doom Patrol">Jeremy Carver</item>
        <item name="Dragon Ball">Akira Toriyama</item>
        <item name="Fairy Tail">Hiro Mashima</item>
        <item name="Family Guy">Seth MacFarlane</item>
        <item name="Game of Thrones">David Benioff &amp; D. B. Weiss</item>
        <item name="Gotham">Bruno Heller</item>
        <item name="Grey's Anatomy">Shonda Rhimes</item>
        <item name="Hanna">David Farr</item>
        <item name="Marvel's Iron Fist">Scott Buck</item>
        <item name="Naruto Shippuuden">Masashi Kishimoto</item>
        <item name="NCIS">Don McGill &amp; Donald P. Bellisario</item>
        <item name="Riverdale">Roberto Aguirre-Sacasa</item>
        <item name="Shameless">Paul Abbott</item>
        <item name="Supergirl">Greg Berlanti, Andrew Kreisberg, &amp; Ali Adler</item>
        <item name="Supernatural">Eric Kripke</item>>
        <item name="The Flash">Geoff Johns, Andrew Kreisberg, &amp; Greg Berlanti</item>
        <item name="The Simpsons">Matt Groening</item>
        <item name="The Umbrella Academy">Steve Blackman</item>
        <item name="The Walking Dead">Frank Darabont</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- categories: 1 = movie; 2 = TV show -->
    <string-array name="movie_category">
        <item name="A Star is Born">1</item>
        <item name="Alita: Battle Angel">1</item>
        <item name="Aquaman">1</item>
        <item name="Avengers: Infinity War">1</item>
        <item name="Bohemian Rhapsody">1</item>
        <item name="Cold Pursuit">1</item>
        <item name="Creed II">1</item>
        <item name="Fantastic Beasts: The Crimes of Grindelwald">1</item>
        <item name="Glass">1</item>
        <item name="How to Train Your Dragon: The Hidden World">1</item>
        <item name="Mary Queen of Scots">1</item>
        <item name="Master Z: Ip Man Legacy">1</item>
        <item name="Mortal Engines">1</item>
        <item name="Overlord">1</item>
        <item name="Ralph Breaks the Internet">1</item>
        <item name="Robin Hood">1</item>
        <item name="Serenity">1</item>
        <item name="Spider-Man: Into the Spider-Verse">1</item>
        <item name="T-34">1</item>
        <item name="Arrow">2</item>
        <item name="Doom Patrol">2</item>
        <item name="Dragon Ball">2</item>
        <item name="Fairy Tail">2</item>
        <item name="Family Guy">2</item>
        <item name="Game of Thrones">2</item>
        <item name="Gotham">2</item>
        <item name="Grey's Anatomy">2</item>
        <item name="Hanna">2</item>
        <item name="Marvel's Iron Fist">2</item>
        <item name="Naruto Shippuuden">2</item>
        <item name="NCIS">2</item>
        <item name="Riverdale">2</item>
        <item name="Shameless">2</item>
        <item name="Supergirl">2</item>
        <item name="Supernatural">2</item>>
        <item name="The Flash">2</item>
        <item name="The Simpsons">2</item>
        <item name="The Umbrella Academy">2</item>
        <item name="The Walking Dead">2</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
</resources>
